It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like the wind, jump high.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going on the stage.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
Know what you're making, my dream time to.
Don't you feel it, I
really don't know what is.
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
The crazy unknown there are no rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wild, girl.
I'm no afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around, oh.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can't do it, so can you only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow, go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like the wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you cannot achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, rolling.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your wife that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, and you want more.
Come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life.
Shine like a star to be good, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Just that you gotta keep your best.
Let's keep on going, I'm not dead.
You make my day every day.
Princess Moncherry, please be safe.
Awesome!
You can see inside the palace
from all the way down here?
Yes.
With my clairvoyance, I can
send my sight wherever I want.
Sanji would kill for that power.
I hope this little princess
doesn't give us a bunch of trouble.
Leo didn't paint a flattering picture.
Called her selfish and
obnoxious and mean-spirited.
Halt! Who goes there?
Halt yourself!
Hey! Kin'emon! Oh! Sir Usopp!
You know him? Yeah! Let him go!
It's a flying weirdo!
No need to fear.
This man is Congido.
I found him at last.
Your, uh, riding bird looks
like it's seen better days.
We were surprised at the state of things.
A great number of people seem
to be rushing to this plateau,
though I could not discern the reason.
Yeah, that's a problem.
Though honestly, I don't think
they'll be able to climb up this high.
Worry not, long-nosed goblin man.
I saw that they were in need,
so I provided them a net.
I predict they will arrive here shortly.
Are you trying to get
me killed, you moron?
God, who stops going down?
Why does this net suck so much?
All those people are
coming here to get me.
What an awful blunder I've made.
My foolishness is truly peerless, And I
did such a thing to my benefactor, no less.
I shall commit Harakiri to show my regret.
Kanjido, don't do it! Okay, I won't.
Fix this?
Or you might as well cut open your belly!
That's it.
There's still one room I haven't checked.
I just want to go back to Green Bed.
Won't anybody come save me?
Can you hear me, Leo? Sure!
Can what's up?
I have located the princess.
I saw her deep in the palace,
hidden away, but she's all right.
Where did they hide her?
She's at the back of the chapel.
The small room—remember,
buried away in the dark—the naughty room?
Yes, that's it!
that's it What's wrong?
I was just thinking of Princess Scarlet.
My mother? Yeah.
When we used to go visit the palace,
Princess Viola and I would pass mischief,
and then King Rick would scold her.
Big sis!
Scarlet, it's you!
You got into trouble again?
Naughty girl. Nuh-uh.
I didn't even break the plate myself.
It was them we only broke it cuz
you told us we could break it.
I said you could touch it
you bunch of little dummies
I'll come and apologize with you
later sure anyway, aren't you hungry?
Uh-huh.
Even when we caused
trouble, she was sweet.
Sorry I got sidetracked there,
but I remember the naughty room.
Thanks, Viola.
That's the enemy's base. Be careful.
Times have changed.
Don't worry!
We won't let this mission fail!
Wait a second.
So, this is the third
level right now, correct?
Yes, almost there.
One more and we'll reach the flower field.
We've been spotted! Incoming!
Even all my most elaborate
fantasies couldn't
prepare me for the real-life Straw Heads.
Hey, Rooster, watch out!
Hot roller!
Are you okay?
This is the ability of the pup-pup fruit!
I'm falling! Oh, no!
My yellow cups are down!
Robin!
Rather audacious, aren't you?
Thinking you can sneak up
to the palace on my watch?
It's Gladius!
Cup!
Diez, blue!
Rebecca, it's up to you now.
Take the key to law.
I can take care of the rest. Robin!
I'm right, dude!
Toys?
That can't be good.
Take this.
Sir Usopp, why must you strike me too?
You're the one who brought him here?
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
are you still looking for something viola
sugar has woken up no
it can't be I beat her
I mean no one can
withstand my special facial
jack-in-a-box technique I was sure she'd
be out cold for a couple of days at least
the rest of your crew
doesn't know anything
about her do they or her ability Straw Hat
and Karin and his current
group are in danger!
She's ready to fight!
IF you have a long nose,
then stay out of my way!
Or on a second, now,
you can just drop dead!
Why?
We just brought some snacks
in case you might be hungry...
Here!
It's just sausages.
They're too long.
Like noses.
I want something nice and round.
Like grapes.
I'll turn you morons
into headcracker dolls.
Now go and protect the palace.
I feel bad for the young master.
I'll transform this whole kingdom.
I'll have to.
They can all be toys.
Oh yes.
And first, I'll get that long-nosed
bastard and the rest of his stupid crew.
Varul, watch out!
Horsey!
Bastard!
Some gobs just pick up!
Varul!
Stay with me.
This is awful.
It crushed its head.
Please, my friend, don't die.
Damn it!
It got back up!
How dare you?
That's my partner!
Light of Beauty, round table!
What?
They keep coming back, no matter what!
Now, Gum-Gum!
UFO!
BIRDS CHIRP
Damn it.
If I only had that key,
I could finish this easy.
What's that?
It's real noisy.
I got sloppy. It's you!
Mr. Luffy! A miracle!
Robin!
Luffy! Treffy! You're down here? Nico!
You brought the key, didn't you?
Give it to me now!
She got away.
Well, she's just one little brat.
Even if she makes it to the palace,
she won't be able to do anything.
I'll kill her when I'm done with you.
The name is Gladius.
And I'm putting an end to this rebellion.
Rooster, let's go.
Luffy: Traffy soldier, go on ahead
to the flower field, get that key.
We can handle this, yep, you sure?
Rebecca's waiting—just go!
Looks
like we made it to the fourth level.
I hope Robin's all right; her friends too?
too
No need to worry!
Ussal and his allies are super tough!
They sure are. You're right.
I'm sorry to leave so suddenly, but we need
to rescue Princess Monchery right away!
Of course.
Is it okay to leave you here alone?
I'll be fine.
Lucy and the others will
be here soon anyway.
Good luck out there.
Thanks!
Stay strong till we
put an end to all this!
Father must be out there
fighting right now, somewhere.
Didn't think you'd make it.
Rebecca.
Of course! Mr.
Luffy, let me take this one.
Roosterhead! Buried! Stairs!
Those balls he throws are explosives.
They'd blow up before you
could bounce them back.
That was cool!
Uh, no, it was nothing.
You're too kind.
What a nuisance.
Stairability!
Stairs!
Huh?
Oh! Awesome!
Now that's handy!
I made it just for you, Mr.
Luffy!
You're facing the wrong way. Thanks, pal!
You're the best!
No, you're the best, and thank you.
Thank you for being born.
Come on.
It's a straight shot to the top.
You ready, Traffy? Just go.
I'm going ahead.
Hey, wait a sec!
You okay?
Spare your concerns, Straw Hat.
I won't die in a place like this.
I still have a score to
settle with these monsters.
Until my dear Farul is avenged, I
refuse to take another step forward!
Loopy, watch out! Bombs!
Leave this to me!
There's a barrier, you fool!
Damn it, Bartolomeo!
I can only make so much barrier at once.
And I'm at my limit.
I used every last inch
making those stairs.
But that's fine by me.
If it helps Mr.
Luffy even a little, then I'm
happy to die right here and now!
You're quite the piece
of work, aren't you?
Tough it out a bit and I'll guard you
until you can use your barriers again.
You don't have any manners, huh?
Cinco monos! Time to fetch!
I know how you feel.
I'm with you, Brewster.
Our captain is something special.
I'd risk anything for him.
Even my life.
Luffy's our trump card.
He's our key to victory.
Mio fleur.
Gigantesco mano.
You're not laying a finger on my captain.
No more screwing around.
You're quite the odd one.
Weren't you trying to stall us?
It doesn't seem like you
should be complaining—how
long are you gonna keep
this act up, old man?
Old
man he says, well that's not
my only disadvantage frankly,
I prefer to take things easy.
I don't discriminate among my enemies.
Scary
kid though, I don't suppose you got your
position by being kind to the elderly.
elderly
Fair enough.
My position doesn't require
me to be kind either.
Don't hold this one against me.
Gravity blade.
Raging Tiger!
Horizontal gravity?
I thought so.
You were holding back.
The problem is, I still don't know why.
you might say this is an
all-or-nothing gamble for me and
the stakes are as big as they get
i'm laying my life on the line
for this one that said i have to
get my dice in order to make my
roll because if i lose them the
game is over before it even starts
this is deplorable Rebecca
you coward why do you
keep running you're a fighter
aren't you sorry I mean
gladiator I thought you
were coming here to kill me
we put on some good entertainment
back at the Coliseum, didn't we?
But if you won't fight me properly,
it's time I dispose of you.
Well, you have nowhere to run now.
Hmm, I know.
Let's make this a little more poetic.
Rebecca wasn't your mother,
also—shot with a gun!
gun
Please, help me, soldier!
Rebecca!
Wait, it can't be!
Kilos!
Keep your hands off her.
You have taken enough from me!
This statue before you,
this man was a legend.
He was the greatest gladiator in the
whole history of the Corrida Coliseum.
I regret I couldn't
save your mother's life,
but I will devote mine to
protect yours, whatever the cost.
Become strong, Rebecca!
Father...
Please forgive me, Rebecca.
As a mere toy without a future,
the only thing I could do
was teach you how to fight.
I know it was hard on you.
You're a gentle soul
just like your mother.
But you need no longer suffer.
Now,
I'll fight for you.
You want to elaborate on that?
Kiros!
I won't just stand by.
I'll make you pay for your treachery!
I'll kill you!
Rebecca!
Lucy?
Lucy!
You made it!
Rebecca!
The key!
Lucy!
You're safe, thank goodness!
What is this?
The key!
Give it to me!
It's right here!
Go, now!
Rebecca!
Ah!
Thru! Thru!
Yes!
Get back here!
We made it, finally!
I'm free, finally.
So this is the fourth
level where Mingo's hiding.
Let's tear this place apart!
Yeah.
Law!
Straw Hat!
It's Diamante. Eeeh!
Eeeh!
You two go ahead without me!
I've got a score to settle with him!
Kill that bastard!
In my stead!
Leave it to me!